compart.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy » Compart

Compart AG is glad about the fact that you decided to visit our website and that you are interested in our company and in our products.

This privacy policy statement is released by Compart in order to inform you about our regulations and measures so that you can feel sure that your personal data will be protected. Your legal concerns regarding the protection of your data will be addressed as follows.

### Personal Data

By personal data it is meant information about your identity. To this category belong for example data regarding your name, address, telephone number and e-Mail address.

### Web Analytics

Data on this website (e.g. your internet browser und operating system, referrer sites , the shortened IP address, country/ city of origin, used search engine, visited pages on our website, etc.) is gathered and saved under consideration of data protection for marketing and site-improvement purposes via third party technologies. A pseudonym user profile can be generated from this data, for which cookies may be used. Cookies are small pieces of text data, which are saved locally in the temporary memory of user’s internet browser. The cookies facilitate the recognition of the internet browser. You can set your browser to notify you about the placement of cookies, which will make the usage of cookies transparent. The data, which is gathered with the third party technologies, will not be used to personally identify the site visitor without the separately given consent of those concerned, nor will it be consolidated with the carrier of the pseudonym. Technical data is evaluated statistically to constantly improve our web presence and make our website more attractive. The data collection and storage can be rejected at any time with future effect under [privacy@compart.com](mailto:privacy@compart.com).

### Use of the Personal Data Collected

The personal data you provide will generally be used in order to reply to your inquiries, process your orders, grant you the access to specific information or offers. With the purpose of fostering customer relations it might be necessary that we, one of our subsidiaries or one of our appointed service companies use these personal data to inform you for example about current offers or to carry out online surveys.  
We will not share or otherwise exploit your personal information nor will we sell it to third parties.

### Links to Other Websites

This privacy policy does not apply when you access external links which can be found on our website. We have no control over the privacy policy of other providers.

### Right of Information

You can obtain information about the data we collected at any time. If required please write to

Compart AG  
Datenschutzbeauftragter  
Otto-Lilienthal-Str. 38  
71034 Böblingen  
Germany

or simply send an e-Mail to [privacy@compart.com](mailto:privacy@compart.com).

### Right of Objection

You can revoke your consent to the collection and retention of your personal information at any time. If required please use the contacts provided in the previous section regarding the right of information. Billing and accounting information will not be affected by the deletion.

### Changes in Our Data Protection Regulations

Our privacy policy can be subjected to changes. Please consider the up-to-date version of our statement.

Back
